it was itself a mining town
there every day
I lived a powerless life
those who lost their jobs after the mine closed
looked for solace in a bottle every day
some even left hastily in search of another life
the remaining miners in official housing awaiting compensation
divided into 2 groups
who had money
drank and played
who didn't have
snapped and took it out on their wives and children
small town
with a chain of murders
gentleman and the police
holding the line
you need to calm down police calm down
you know me
calm down it doesn't concern you
please calm down
mind your own business
you're fine hey
yes sir
take a breath hey
don't resort to violence
speak in words
you ratted me out
don't resort to violence
tell me why you called the cops
come on come on
I'll fucking kill you
take your jacket here
let's go oh come on in
stop it
come here
I copral Jeong Hoi from the Unsan Police Station
if you need help
just blink at me
I'll help you
what are you doing
come inside
madam what are you doing with this filthy cop
come up here now
I still have to teach you a lesson
every day on patrol
everything I could
it's giving people signals
even realizing that it is useless
I couldn't stop
this city was completely enveloped
atmosphere of crime
I couldn't leave this place
I didn’t notice how this hell penetrated my soul
while I was just watching
How's another day going?
it finally dawned on you
say thank you
that this is not boiling water
hey
how dare you address me like that
to the noble husband
hey now you understand I understand
speak
he thought that there must be a well here somewhere
because we are in the village
and even in the hospital
Is he the god of investigations?
why are his guesses always correct?
he really always guesses everything right
I'm not the only one who thinks
that's weird
he must have a secret
suguwan
he got everything out of him by deception
realized about 1 murder of a young man
Lord, that's what it's all about, but why?
he knew about the hospital and the well
he knew about everything
but pretended not to know
no no no no
it's not like that no no but
why does this bother me so much
not
what are you doing
you can't be here
come out now
oh soo yeol yes
when she was little
we lost her mother
we were left alone
we didn't have a good relationship
we barely spoke
and she was almost never home
she was just waiting
to leave home
what happened
you're hungry
who is this signal for?
what signal
this one
did you wear this yesterday
you spilled something
why wash after 1 time?
ishin
I'm not that petty
you're hiding something
can you tell me
what are you hiding
ishin what are you hiding from me
when I became an adult
she immediately left home
I could barely find her
interviewing everyone
and shin why do you always hide something from me
I found out that her husband
was known around town as trash
what are you hiding from me
I saw clearly
what was her life like
but I couldn't do anything for her
out of anxiety I visited her secret several times
just to find out
how is she doing
I was there that night too stop it
how could you
you should have made her give in
or at least report it to the police
if you had told me then
we could stop it at least then
after that she killed five more
this woman killed them
why did you just do nothing? I wanted to
Well, I just couldn’t bring myself to
I couldn't do that to my daughter
I'm her father, I can't ruin my child's life like that.
yes I know
I'm selfish
I committed an unforgivable sin
with remorse in my soul
I raised you
and even took other children
but this does not correct what was done
I will never stop paying for my sin
anyway
the current killer knows about it
did you tell someone
who would I tell this to?
no one knows
anyway soool
you should end this
she can be considered dead
I even made her grave
all this time
we lived as if she really died
the whole world may not know
but you know you're sitting here today
because we did it all
I know
but that's my job
if you continue dating your mother
you think everything will end
when the work is done
the world doesn't work like that
you have to be the one
who will catch this killer
my birth mother
claims that I am the reason for her 1 murder
I have to catch him
this woman killed six
and now there's a bastard
who follows in her footsteps
now
we have 10 victims
I am to blame for the beginning of these 10 murders
I need to catch the killer
그래야아빠돼
I can live my life
the criminal knew part of your past
which even the police didn't know
so let's start with yonpo
then these people were your neighbors
maybe you remember any of them
criminal record police department
I don't see Namba
how could he have witnessed the incident with my father
quite possible
he was our neighbor after all
but he was also an alcoholic and a scumbag
assault harassment and persistent gaming
he had a penchant
and what are the chances
that he's a copycat killer
remember anything
jeongyeon
she is unshakable
she will stay with you even after that
how the whole world will know about me
then I would leave
are you going to leave this district office employee
soguwan
then
what should I do
should I kill him
can you do it
I'll do it
what
when you feel uncomfortable or unpleasant
you're just killing a person
related to this
I'm not like that
I will protect mine 7
You can stop this performance already with concern for your family
let this be your warning next time
I'm sorry I won't ask
remember anything about him
his son
do you remember him
yes
what about him
his mother left
when he was still little
he was very lonely as a child
and quite emotionally fragile
he was always at our house
one day I noticed a wound on his body
and every day he had a new one
child abuse
I went to his damn father
you scared me
아
민재는 실제로 학대를 받은
거보다 더 심한
I could only take care of him to the extent
their capabilities
and what
that's all
that's not enough he saw me
I'm sure when he saw me on the news
he realized that I was using cola with anesthesia
when he realized
that I came to kill his father
how do you think he felt
he believed that Jeong and Shin came to save him
yes it seems like that
Pak Menchi is now registered over there, it looks like
he still lives with pak on bae
yeah he still can't leave this place
despite that
that I never received real love there
but he had someone
who was even ready to kill for him
for him there must be jeon and shin
was like a mother
and maybe more
then you think
so he follows in her footsteps
not sure
but I know for sure
that he deliberately lured me to the well
as a reminder of my past
he knows me
Park Minjae knows
what do I look like
he may already be next to me
when I heard
that your father is missing
it seemed strange to me
but I couldn't figure it out
we didn't have time
politicians were breathing down our backs
we relied only on that
what did chen and shin say?
investigating a hidden case was a luxury
which we didn't have
this is the case
let's keep your father's business a secret for now
if it becomes public
your mother's identity will be revealed
I'll take care of Park Minjae
and you be careful
I will contact you
Sooyool's husband
you're feeling better now
Why are you frozen, you’re standing in front of your mother-in-law?
say you're sorry
what Suyola suspected
and introduce yourself
Jeon and Shin
it looks like someone comes to her sometimes
he said this is house 1
which is visible
at the end of the forest path near the beach
it's probably him
but the house looks abandoned
no one seems to live here
hey no need
hey
stop, you can't just come in like that
it's creepy here
I think we've already seen everything
let's go back and now this is someone else's house
let's go
I can't do it anymore
chunyeon
who are you chunyeon who are you
hello sir
this was my husband's childhood home
we'll just take a quick look around and leave
sir can
go have a drink at our expense
and we'll leave soon really
dad what are you doing
give her back her money
dad
I don't want her money back
sorry, you must have been scared
my dad a little
wait
here
no no no
everything is fine, it's our own fault
everything is fine
take it I don't want
so that people think badly about the village
please take it
I heard a little of your conversation
if your husband lived here
you are Jeong and Shin's sister-in-law
you know jeon and shin
I know aunty and shin well
she was in her 20s then
she was young for an aunt
but then we called all married people that way
this is my phone
medicine time for my dad
sorry have a nice tour
sorry again
maybe you can send him some more hearts
go catch him
hey he's not my type at all
I actually have my own standards
I asked
doesn't embarrass me in front of others
damn
I know
I'm sorry
that's not what I meant
there are no cars available nearby
what's the point of buying a car?
even if you don't know how to drive
for beauty and what
it looks like we really are in the village
not a single taxi around
I found this at my home
this is a photo of my aunt and me on the beach
wow she's so beautiful
you've never seen her photo before
no, I didn’t see it, I understand
sorry but this is my only photo
I can't give it to you
can I take a picture of him of course?
if you are going back
I can give you a ride
if you want, I'll go back too
we ourselves would be great
ok, I'll put my things away now
seats a minute
and what can you ask him about Suyol’s childhood?
It would be better to take a taxi
yes everything is fine
하세요
Park Minja has a business license
type of activity security business
looks like it's some kind of detective agency
where is my address
but it's been closed for a long time
where are you at home
I can't reach Chunyeon on the phone
this has never happened before
I'm worried so I'm waiting for her
I'll call you back later brother
jongho is it you
yeah wait sooyoung now
yes
what happened
you don't remember me
it's me pahminje
way to support a person oh yes
we were in yumpo
what were you doing there
ok I have to go
take care of yourself
here are the dried slices
cod local delicacy
simpo souvenir
Well, why don’t you remember him?
he said that
lived next door
민제 민제 박민제
박민제 다 맞지
아기하네 그러네 그러네 그러네
그러네 그러네
well you're almost done with this webpton
yes
the killer will be caught after 5 people die
there will be about 0 victims
Pakhminja's car is now parked in front of my house
true how
I'll explain later
first write down the car number and find out where it is registered
minjae and you don't drink so where should you go
yeah I'll just drink some water
but it's still like that
are you sure about the lip color?
isn't he handsome
almost the same
it's something like a grapefruit
that I don't really like grapefruit
what did you do in yonpo
we got out of the city and stopped on the way back
what's going on
you can join
of course
possible but by chance
you don't have ketchup
dried cod tastes best with ketchup
chunya look at him
he says it's me
you know, listen
what is it?
some resemblance
yes true
he is a webtoon artist after all
you can sign below
I'll make money if you become famous
it's nice that you say that
like I won't
wait
stop and I'll draw you
perfect
you really don't remember
when we were little
taught the townspeople how to cut meat
crab and stuff
I don't know why I don't remember this at all
you're fine
wait
then
you don't remember the praying mantis thing
praying mantis
doesn't everyone know about this?
maybe not
then the world championship was going on
what is this
serial killer
it was a complete mess back then
if you cross the bridge from yonpo
there is a mining town
there's a sleigh over there
there is 1 young woman
killed five
five why?
but he knows more about this than me
he's a policeman here
no, I don’t know much myself
it's an old thing
then I'll tell you
they said she was about 20
and for some reason her face and name were not revealed
she became known by the nickname Mantis
she brutally killed only men
who abused women and children
honestly
her victims did much worse things
no matter how terrible it is
this doesn't mean you can kill people
That's why there are laws, right?
you're a policeman after all
but if you look at it from an artist's point of view
I honestly think
that the praying mantis had great empathy
she was very sensitive to the suffering of others
so those men
who abused women and children also experienced the same pain
and pull yourself together
it was murder
no more
she killed a man
I know I know
but I kind of understand his point
I think if I were the family of the victims it would make me feel better
they were freed from their offenders
but to be honest
I was always more interested
her son than herself
she had a son
Yes, this was reported in the news, of course
mother is a serial killer
I wonder how he is now
he must be about our age
true
why are you contacting him?
like he's older
aren't you 1 age?
there is a story connected with this too
when we were little I broke my side mirror
on someone's car
playing ball hey where
he's the devil
where is your home
forgive me let me go oh you brat
where is your house you told me
that you live nearby
oh you brat
listen this is your son
yes
this is my son
what about
she had such warm hugs
aunt paid for the mirror
from that day I was there almost every day
your mom seems nice
so why did his eldest do it exactly
it seems that the man really doubted
that I'm her son
then he turned to Suyol and asked
Am I really his older brother?
soool then said no
he is my little brother
that's what he said
but then I was taller than him
I'm fine
from that day on I call him big brother
my father didn't like it
but I practically lived in that house
aunt truth
treated me like a son
but that accident
just took her without warning
what what's wrong with me
the evening was great
yes come again okay
bye bye
bye macaw get there safe
why did you actually go to yonpo
I wanted to make sure
that your mother really died
you must be
I heard my conversation with Mr. Jeong on the street
your phone rang
and I picked up the phone
Mr. Jeong suddenly said
that you shouldn't see your mom
he sounded very worried
well
there was a grave in yonpo
now everything is clear
well, let's all go back
you don't want this
yes
what
you don't want a child what
where did you get the idea
don't pretend
I think everything is connected
this is a problem and a family
which you are hiding
jeongyeon
you drank a lot
we'll talk later
so you're not going to tell me yeah
jeongyeon what's wrong with you
boss whose chun ho
seoyeon dongnam gwanggu gwangju
your phone rang
and I picked up the phone
Mr. Jeong suddenly said
that you shouldn't see your mom
pakminge descendant
I'm going to the parking lot
songshin pi n pi print sharply binding
what are you doing
it can be called
timid flirtation
minjae
let's get to know each other better
I'll call you
good
speedy pakminge detective agency
Chun Shin
where are you in the parking lot it looks like
pakmin lives here
that you don't even have a warrant hey
get out of there now
I'm already on my way
I told you I felt him next to me
I was right
this bastard has been watching me this whole time
and why not him and if he understands
what we know will go to the bottom
hey what the
damn
hello sir
are you okay sir
I lost it
Sooyool you need to get out of there now okay
what the hell
you're dead
it was you
you killed them all
what who
have you met her
isn't it
discuss a murder case shut up
please tell me
with our mother
everything is fine
hello madam
yes hello
I'll inform the accountant ok
restricted area
sorry
please forgive me
저는신
저는신저는신
Mr. Suguwan
can you hear me
what are you doing
what did you just give me
아
you say
that I killed someone
this thing
there would be peace
if only this was enough to defeat someone
you live in the world and know so little about it
what's going on in the dark
when they catch cheaters you think
they feel ashamed and hide under the covers
not at all
they look back and rush at you without any clothes
do you think this is enough
yes of course
December 7
tell me what you did from 2100 until midnight
I don't know, I guess
what were you doing
do you remember exactly
what did you do last week
Park Minjae are you a suspect in this case?
think before you answer
you're really so cool
so that's what you're like at work
It's a pity that mom didn't see
I asked about December 7
Looks like your mom is a big irritant for you
veins swell
as soon as I mentioned her
ok good
Why is there strong competition even in this area now?
expense reports are just the beginning
I have to send to the client clockwise
report on your actions
I make sure to share my location with them
you can see exactly
what I was doing and where I was at those hours
Mr. Suguwan
look at me
everything's ok
sir, where do you see me?
look at me look
we met at the station
it's so stuffy here
I can't breathe
my hand hurts a lot
could you help me
please save me
please
it's better that way
thank you
she's going to kill someone to kill
me
who will kill you
Mantis Jeong and Shin are now in prison
I heard that
the recent murder looks a bit like killing a praying mantis
quickly forget about everything else
what matters is who deserves death
right
looks like the boss is here 1
Looks like you want to hide me from the other cops
they can't know
about you and mom
you really need it
I should shut up
you're a real nuisance
I'm not trying to make your life difficult
fake grave
which you arranged
to hide this secret
I'll take it all to my grave
by the way
can you let me see my mom just once?
you're not going anywhere
until we confirm
that it was you on this route
and not just your phone got it
can I have some water
time for my meds
you don't know anything
yes you are right
I don't know that's why I'm here
why is chun shin trying to kill you
because I know everything
I'm a policeman
i can protect you
zero victim chuna shin
only you knew about it correctly
you can tell me I will protect you
you couldn't even protect your own son
and you're talking about that guy
who loves ketchup
of course I know him
he is a regular customer
he wasn't here on the night of December 7th by any chance
so wait
I remember he said
that I'm very busy
came almost every night for pork chops
소구한 소구한 소구한
yes detective kim suguwan did
why go away I'm from the police
madam he got out of the hospital
damn
아
here is active
captain I'll look from here to there
and you can look there
you're fine
yes I'm fine
sorry
soguwan
속만
속만 속만
that's enough
stop it
why can't I get it
why does everyone leave me
why is it always just me
suguwan
bastard stop following me already
수고했어
sokwan what was that
there was an accident near the gwanhyeon intersection in front of the bank
booguan this is an emergency
Suguwan is on his way soon
save your strength don't move
why
didn't you want this
because I know
praying mantis about you
and about your damn wife
I'll tell everyone about them
what did you say
you
you want me dead too
no
when you shot yourself I saved you
there were other cops around then
1 blood
you
just like your mother
I envy you
damn
It turns out Nateina raised butter beetles
bathroom ventilation
where there were no cameras
and fed me poison
which I collected from them
it was my mistake
damn
I'm sorry
she took your shoes too
why did you do this
what did you say to him?
that you hurt him
I'm sorry captain
why did you release him
from handcuffs
if they hadn't screwed him up like that
he would still be alive
but the driver who hit him and disappeared
what if it wasn't an accident
but intentionally as soon as Soguwan left the alley
the driver hit him
as if that was their goal
before hiding
who could it be
what if
This is the serial killer's way of silencing Soguwan.
you remember zero corpse
he must have known something about jung won shik's case
and that's why it's enough
I'm the group leader
you should have warned me in advance detective kim
you have a complaint against me
everything was so
too bad you just ignored the protocol
you don't trust me at all
tell me straight
what do you think
I have no thoughts
you're angry that I'm your team leader right
if it weren't for me
you would be the team leader right
they say you had a lot of problems in the drug department
think you'll stay here
if you do it again
for example, if the whole team disobeys you
you are threatening me now
that's not why we didn't follow your instructions
that you are a leader
but because they thought
that it would be better for business
if they thought differently and it helps the investigation
1 more person died
want to continue
while his blood is still on our hands
we haven't even come close to solving the culprit
what if someone dies
we're still looking
what then what then
It's not only hard for you
it's difficult for all of us
to all of us
please excuse me
I need that driver who hit him
Mr. Jongho
hello
are you crazy
so what the hell
you did it for 4 hours
who's there
or what now
hi
forgotten serial killer
which everyone was thinking about
is actually alive and running somewhere nearby
you killed suguwan
answer yourself first
at least you feel a little better
hearing that he was dead
Pak Min has already been released
pull yourself together
stop idolizing this vile serial killer
and just live a normal life
this is a dating app
woman named chui
all 4 victims follow her profile
give the phone to that woman
to that woman what is he talking about